## **DOMINIK GOLEBIEWSKI**

### **Database Developer**

#### **SUMMARY**

Organised and self-motivated Database Developer with 4+ years of success designing and implementing database solutions in Snowflake and DBT. Goal-orientated with ability to understand business problems and create systems to improve functionality. Work effectively independently and in collaborative settings.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Database Developer

10/2019 - Present

#### **Atheon Analytics**

Fully Remote, UK

Designed and implemented database solutions for high volume, high performance projects resulting in increase efficiency.

- Developed effective modular SQL and Jinja scripts utilising DBT and Snowflake, resulting in enhanced performance.
- Designed internal database tools utilising Snowflake, Streamlit, and Python to enhance productivity and cycle time.
- Developed a testing framework and an internal DBT package to facilitate case tests for data pipelines.
- Refactored transformation architecture resulting in a ~70% performance increase and ~60% Snowflake credits reduction.
- Designed and implemented the back-end database that provides data to the BI tool Tableau and the end user.
- Supported junior developers and customer support with database-related questions, resulting in increased productivity and quicker delivery.
- Achieved Snowflake SnowPro Core accreditation.

#### Junior Database Developer

10/2018 - 10/2019

#### **Atheon Analytics**

Cranfield, UK

Participated in the redesign and rollout of new ETL processes.

- Enhanced customer satisfaction and expedited delivery by assisting customer support with database queries.
- Participated in the redesign and implementation of ETL processes for legacy customer data outside of normal business hours to ensure timely and errorfree data migration.
- Improved understanding of the most recent technologies, Python, and the Snowflake data warehouse in the Cloud.

#### **SQL** Developer

09/2016 - 10/2018

#### **XPO Logistics**

Milton Keynes, UK

Developed internal reports and dashboards in Microstrategy and PL/SQL

- Developed database application automation using Visual Basic and Excel VBA.
- · Data analysis using Excel and PL/SQL.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Degree and Field of Study

2008 - 2012

Pawel Wlodkowic University College in Plock

Płock, PL

#### **STRENGTHS**

## ★ Efficient Problem Solver

Proven ability to design and create efficient solutions that deliver results, even for high-volume, high-performance projects.

### ☆ Team Player

Collaborative worker who builds strong relationships with cross-functional teams to drive successful outcomes.

## □ Effective Communicator

Excellent interpersonal and communication skills, with a track record of presenting complex ideas to both technical and non-technical stakeholders.

#### **SKILLS**

Snowflake · Database design ·

 ${\sf Data\ modeling\cdot Data\ warehousing\cdot}$ 

ETL processes · DBT ·

Performance tuning ·

Query optimization

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### Database Optimization Project

Led an initiative to optimize database performance, resulting in a ~70% improvement in query response times.

# Data MigrationProject

Participated in a complex data migration project, ensuring no data was lost and all systems were up and running on schedule.



**EDUCATION** 

IT Technician

Date period

Plocki Uniwersytet Ludowy

Płock, PL

A-Levels

Date period

**Grammar School** 

Ladek Zdroj, PL

**LANGUAGES** 

Polish English Native

Proficient